Tufts Roundtable UP067
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Roundtable
2008 -- 2011
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tisch College
UP067
0.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the full run of the Tufts Roundtable. The Johathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service sponsors the Tufts Roundtable. During the first year of publication, the Journal included the subtitle, 'The Journal of Political Discourse.' During the second year of publication, the subtitle was changed to 'The Journal of Debate and Ideas.'
- Tufts Roundtable, 2008 -- 2011; UP067.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This collection contains the full run of the Tufts Roundtable. The Johathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service sponsors the Tufts Roundtable. During the first year of publication, the Journal included the subtitle, 'The Journal of Political Discourse.' During the second year of publication, the subtitle was changed to 'The Journal of Debate and Ideas.'
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts Roundtable, 2008-11; UP067.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    The Journal of Political Discourse
    Volume
    1
  - Tufts Roundtable, 2008-12; UP067.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    2
  - Tufts Roundtable, 2009-03; UP067.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    3
  - Tufts Roundtable, 2009-04; UP067.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    4
  - Tufts Roundtable, 2009-10; UP067.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    The Journal of Debate and Ideas; (renumbering)
    Volume, issue
    2, 1
  - Tufts Roundtable, 2009-12; UP067.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    The Journal of Debate and Ideas
    2, 2
  - Tufts Roundtable, 2010-03; UP067.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    The Journal of Debate and Ideas; Issue is mislabeled as 2009.
    2, 3
  - Tufts Roundtable, 2010-04; UP067.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    Journal of Political Discourse
    2, 4
  - Tufts Roundtable, 2010-10; UP067.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    3, 1
  - Tufts Roundtable, 2011-03; UP067.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    Journal of Debate and Ideas
    3, 2
  - Tufts Roundtable, 2011-10; UP067.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    4, 1
  - Tufts Roundtable, 2011-12; UP067.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    4, 2